Hello, welcome to my channel, this is a
short video about my experience.
I have an insurance company, Tata Egg, and one of its employees had a
minor accident in my car,
and I gave it for repair
to the Mahindra workshop. Many
parts of it are damaged, so only two
parts have been repaired. I mean, whoever I told
for the survey, I will take the name of that person. If you are
watching this video, you will understand automatically,
and the leadership of Tata Egg will also know
who I am talking about. So
here I want to say that
you should not keep such employees with you
because they are only and only spoiling the name of the company for
their own benefits, for
their personal benefits, any
company does not want their
customers to get the full experience, so here these
such employees are the ones
who spoil the name of the company, so
look, the entire damage to the car has happened here, the tractor
trolley was stuck here, because of that.  It has
completely gone to the back, so
when we are opening the gate,
look here, there is a sound,
it is broken from here, the entire headlight is separate, the
rest is this center one,
and here this entire bumper and after that there is
DRL, so Banda had come
and every time I am telling him that DRL has to be done
but he is refusing, now
in this drill it is possible that this can happen in the rain
or it can get stuck in winter,
so the meaning of taking a policy is
that when Banda is taking a policy, then whatever
damage is there in the car, that damage should be completely checked, I do
n't know, Banda comes and the inspector goes and makes
three rounds, he does
not check completely what all the damages are in the car, it has been
a week, it has not been cleaned yet
and the poor workshop people go in between, the
customers tell them that they are
not getting this work repaired, they do not know
that the reason is of the insurance company
and secondly, look at this scratch here,
you can see the scratch clearly, when
I parked the car from the front, the
tractor driver was coming in reverse gear
Now to save myself from that I took it out from the side and
this is also not done
and look here this is a small scratch on the
chin of the tractor, it is there,
maybe he is refusing, so
tell me what is the meaning of paying 20000 rupees a year, this
sir, first send the approval,
only the headlight
was damaged and the center one is also damaged and the
left side front, I
asked him what is the reason why you have not done these things, then he
said that
sir these things are not done, there are scratches in these,
these things are not done, so I said no
problem, you leave it, you are not doing it,
whatever approval you are sending, you send it,
then I will select it further, so
today I sent an email to
Tata Ag customer support and their
handling team,
I wrote in it that my
repair has been done and these things are there, so as soon as I
reached the workshop, the
approval was immediately sent to the workshop people
that sir your DRL and this has also been approved, that is why
I am asking this  If this
thing was not approved then why have you
proved it now, why did you not approve it before the email, so
here this individual
person will have some benefit, that is why he did
not give approval, so this is a small video,
I just want to intimate that
person that if such
customers come in future then this should not happen to those customers
and Tata Insurance has doors for such people, that
too is not covered yet, their
approval has not come, so until I get the complete
approval, I will
not start the car and if you
cannot give the approval then email me,
this is the reason I am not giving the approval, if there is a clause in my
insurance policy that there is
no word on scratches, then
you send it to me, I will agree to that
thing, otherwise I will fight for this thing, I will have to go to the
court,
I will fight and no matter how much time it takes,
so much time has already been wasted, so
I have no problem
I will fight where I am right, so this is a small short
video and the detailed video of this,
I will upload it in two-three days
because I need a lot of data for it, I will have to do some
erection to make the video, so
I will upload a good special video and
for this bond of Tata Egg Insurance, the
experience I have had with it and the way
it has treated me, thank you for watching
and please like, share and subscribe this
video.